(Amy:)Stubbed his toe on the
revolving door on the way in.
(Sheldon:)You know those confounded
things make me dizzy.
(Amy:)Who told you
to keep going around?
(Sheldon:)There was a large
plant in the lobby.
(Sheldon:)It kept looking
like the outside.
(Penny:)Okay, listen,
when Leonard comes out,
(Penny:)he is not gonna feel great,
(Penny:)so, please don't
give him a hard time.
(Amy:)Penny has a good point.
(Amy:)This is like the man
in the supermarket
(Amy:)with the goiter on his neck.
(Amy:)Whatever you're thinking,
just keep it to yourself.
(Sheldon:)It was like a grapefruit.
(Amy:)And I'm sure he knew that
(Amy:)before you held
a grapefruit up next to it.
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm not
making any promises.
(Sheldon:)Not only did Leonard take what
I feel is an unnecessary risk,
(Sheldon:)he deceived me.
(Penny:)Okay, the reason
he deceived you is
(Penny:)you were being
a pain in the ass.
(Sheldon:)The reason I was being
a pain in the B is
(Sheldon:)because I was worried about
him, and no one else was.
(Penny:)Really? You won't
even say "A"?
(Sheldon:)You bet your
sweet B I won't.
(Penny:)Obviously, I care
about Leonard.
(Penny:)I'm gonna spend the rest
of my life with him.